arv\_patil@yahoo.com

Cell: 9850161124



### **Profile:**

Worked extensively on system analysis, design, development, testing and implementation of projects (Complete SDLC) and capable of handling responsibilities independently as well as a proactive team member. Having twenty four year of IT experience and up to 3 years relevant experience of MSBI.

# **Current Work:**

- 10 years of extensive experience in SQL Server database development/administration, development databases as a Developer/DBA in different domains of companies including medium and small scale Industries.
- Involved in the Business Analysis of the OLTP/OLAP data and in decision support.
- Hands on Experience in installing, configuring, managing, monitoring and troubleshooting SQL Server 2014/2012/2008 R2/2005.
- Strong knowledge of Data Warehousing facts & dimensions.
- Experienced in BI Development and Deployment of SSIS packages from MS Access, Excel.
- Extensive experience in MS SQL Server 2014/2012/2008 R2/2005 Business Intelligence in MS SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS) and MS SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS).
- Proficient in Creating, Configuring and Fine-tuning ETL workflows designed in MS SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS).
- Experienced in providing Logging, Error handling by using Event Handlers, and Custom Logging for SSIS Packages.
- Proficient in designing and scheduling complex SSIS Packages for transferring data from multiple data sources to SQL server.
- Hands on experience in creating indexed views, complex stored procedures, effective functions, and appropriate triggers to assist efficient data manipulation and data consistency.
- Experienced in programming Tasks-Stored Procedures, Triggers and Cursors using SQL Server 2014/2012/2008 R2 with T-SQL.
- Experienced in designing, creating, processing of cubes using SSAS.
- Experienced in database administration for MS SQL Server databases, and supported applications with efficient back-end processing.
- Strong Knowledge on Power BI to import data from various sources such as SQL Server, MS Excel etc. strong knowledge of DAX
- Quick learner and good performer both in team and independent job environments

arv\_patil@yahoo.com

Cell: 9850161124



# **EXPERIENCE SUMMARY**

IT Consultant.

From Dec.1015 To Aug 2020.

InfoWorld Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

From Dec.2011 To 30 July 2015 As Developer

Mascon computer services pvt. Ltd. Pune (BPO)

From 23 Aug 2010 To Jan 2012 as Programmer

**Vritti Solustion** 

From Jully 2008 to sep 2009 as Developer

InfoWorld Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

From Dec. 2004 to Nov. 2007 Team Leader Customer support.

Autosoft

From Nov 1997 to Aug. 2004 as Project Leader

InfoWorld Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

From July 96 to Oct 97 as Software Support Developer

Indrayani InfoTech Pvt. Ltd.

From Feb 95 to Jun 96 Customer support executive

Pradeep Jagtap & Co. (CA)

From 94 to 95 as Account Assistant (Manual Accounting)

### **EDUCATION:**

• B.Com from Pune University in 1993

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

SSIS,SSAS,SSRS,POWER BI,Tally Erp 9 and Prime Developer.Visual Basic. Ms Excel. MS Office.PHP,CSS,HTM.

#### **Personal Details**

Name : Arvind Manohar Patil.

Address : B9/9 Indira Nagar (Lower), Bibwewadi Pune 411037

**Birthdate** : 06/03/1970 **Contact** : +919850161124

Email : arv\_patil@yahoo.com, arv\_patil@rediffmail.com

Blog : https://arv2017.blogspot.com